{
    "question": "To avoid scaling issues in Agile deliveries, the organisation SHOULD apply which of the following options?",
    "correct": "red",
    "red": "Explain to them the cost of finding defects at the end of a project can be massive and outweigh the cost of testing incrementally throughout the project.",
    "green": "Accept this and add a few sprints at the end of the project for testing and bug fixing.",
    "blue": "Ask them to test at least the most important features.",
    "yellow": "Accept this and have the development team test the project themselves."
}{
    "question": "Select the roles prescribed by the Kanban development method.",
    "correct": "green",
    "green": "Increased customer satisfaction through regular feedback.",
    "blue": "Agile gives instant benefit.",
    "yellow": "No planning is required.",
    "red": "The same work can be completed with fewer developers."
}{
    "question": "Which of the following would NOT be considered a practice that would help a team achieve continuous delivery?",
    "correct": "green",
    "green": "Initiating",
    "red": "None of these",
    "blue": "Storming",
    "yellow": "Forming"
}{
    "question": "What should be the course of action when a Scrum team discovers their inability to complete the stories included in their sprint, during a daily stand-up?",
    "correct": "green",
    "green": "Neither Product Owner. or Development team",
    "yellow": "Development team.",
    "blue": "Both Product Owner. and Development team",
    "red": "Product Owner."
}{
    "question": "You are working with an agile team, which of the observations below would be an example of them applying an agile way of working?",
    "correct": "green",
    "green": "All of these",
    "yellow": "Wrong products development",
    "red": "Products not meeting the requirements",
    "blue": "Lack of trust between developers and the business users"
}{
    "question": "When an Agile team has created an iteration or sprint plan with an Agile Product Owner, which of the following statements is NOT true?",
    "correct": "red",
    "red": "Agile can cope with complex changing environments.",
    "green": "Agile cannot cope with chaotic or disordered environments.",
    "blue": "Agile removes the need for documentation.",
    "yellow": "Agile projects do not use any planning."
}{
    "question": "The Lean Muda or seven deadly wastes does not includes __________________.",
    "correct": "green",
    "green": "Process Of Ongoing Improvement.",
    "blue": "Process Of Ongoing Interactions.",
    "red": "Process Of Ongoing Involvement.",
    "yellow": "Process Of Ongoing Iterations."
}{
    "question": "The primary advantages of using Agile over traditional methods, is _________________.",
    "correct": "red",
    "red": "Approach the Product Owner and negotiate the scope of the lowest priority stories.",
    "green": "Quietly schedule a few late nights hoping to finish the work on time.",
    "blue": "Bring a few extra people into the team to help them complete all of the stories.",
    "yellow": "Decide to de-scope the lowest priority stories."
}{
    "question": "When software development is delivered using a linear software development life cycle this means that?",
    "correct": "yellow",
    "yellow": "Most of the stories get prioritized as “must do”.",
    "blue": "It is not compatible with Agile.",
    "green": "Teams find it difficult to use.",
    "red": "The output cannot be used for planning."
}{
    "question": "What is the disadvantage of using MoSCoW prioritization?",
    "correct": "blue",
    "blue": "Exploratory Testing",
    "yellow": "Partially done work",
    "red": "Relearning",
    "green": "Extra features"
}